export const EDCQuiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: `The branch of engineering which deals 
      with current conduction through a vacuum or gas
      or semiconductor ? `,
      answer1: "Electricity",
      answer2: "Electrolysis",
      answer3: "Electronics ",
      answer4: "Electrochemistry",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "1A",
    },

    {
      question: "The electronic devices that are capable of performing the following functions except ?",
      answer1: "Amplification",
      answer2: "Rectification  ",
      answer3: "Control",
      answer4: "Electrolysis",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "1B",
    },

    {
      question: `The two most frequently used semiconductor materials are ?`,
      answer1: "Germanium and Silicon",
      answer2: "Germanium and Copper  ",
      answer3: "Silicon and Aluminum ",
      answer4: "Aluminum and  Copper",
      correctAnswer: "answer1",
      key: "1C",
    },

    {
      question: `The main two types of rectification are ?`,
      answer1: "Quarter wave and Full wave",
      answer2: "Quarter wave and Short wave",
      answer3: "Full wave and Half wave ",
      answer4: "Half wave and Quarter wave",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "1D",
    },

    {
      question: "How many diodes are employed in a full-wave bridge rectifier ? ",
      answer1: "1",
      answer2: "2",
      answer3: "3",
      answer4: "4",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "1E",
    },
  ],
};

export const RCMQuiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Electromagnetic waves are radiated by ? ",
      answer1: "Electric Charges ",
      answer2: "Magnetic Charges",
      answer3: "Dynamic Charges ",
      answer4: "Electrolytic Charges",
      correctAnswer: "answer1",
      key: "2A",
    },

    {
      question: "Mode of transmission of Analog signal include ?",
      answer1: "Demodulation and Frequency",
      answer2: "Amplitude modulation and Signal modulation ",
      answer3: "Amplitude modulation and Frequency modulation ",
      answer4: "Frequency modulation and signal modulation",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "2B",
    },

    {
      question: `_____ is a necessary component 
      parts of all electronic devices that communicate by radio?`,
      answer1: "Receiver",
      answer2: "Transmitter",
      answer3: "Transducer ",
      answer4: "Alternator",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "2C",
    },

    {
      question: "The process of encoding information onto a radio wave by varying one of its basic characteristics is? ",
      answer1: "Transmission ",
      answer2: "Modulation ",
      answer3: "Reception ",
      answer4: "Broadcasting ",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "2D",
    },

    {
      question: "The process of extracting radio signal is called ? ",
      answer1: "Modulation ",
      answer2: "Demodulation ",
      answer3: "Mobilization ",
      answer4: "Demobilization ",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "2E",
    },
  ],
};

export const RAFQuiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "The output final stage of a multi-stage amplifier is also called?",
      answer1: "Mixer Stage",
      answer2: "Power Stage",
      answer3: "Detector Stage",
      answer4: "R.F Stage",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "3A",
    },

    {
      question: `The first few stages in this 
      multistage amplifier have the function of 
      only ?`,
      answer1: "Current amplification ",
      answer2: "Frequency amplification ",
      answer3: "Voltage amplification   ",
      answer4: "Amplitude amplification",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "3B",
    },

    {
      question: "The range of human hearing extends from ___ ?",
      answer1: "20 kHz to 30 kHz  ",
      answer2: " 20 Hz to 20 kHz  ",
      answer3: " 20 Hz to 40 kHz   ",
      answer4: " 40 Hz to 40 kHz ",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "3C",
    },

    {
      question: "Which of these parameters is not a transistor parameter?",
      answer1: "Current Gain",
      answer2: "Input Impedance ",
      answer3: "Output Impedance",
      answer4: "Input Frequency",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "3D",
    },

    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a class of amplifier?",
      answer1: "Class A",
      answer2: "Class D",
      answer3: "Class C",
      answer4: "Class B",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "3E",
    },
  ],
};

export const STRQuiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: `There are basically three types of
       satellites according to the function it 
       performs. Which of these is not a type of 
       satellite ?`,
      answer1: "Fixed Service Satellites",
      answer2: "Consumer Satellites",
      answer3: "Medium Powered Satellite",
      answer4: "Low Noise Density Satellite",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "4A",
    },

    {
      question: `Low Noise Block Converter (LNB) 
      serves as signal ?`,
      answer1: "Modulator and diplexer ",
      answer2: "Modulator and multiplexer ",
      answer3: "Amplifier",
      answer4: "Modulator and Uplink",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "4B",
    },

    {
      question:"The main components of a satellite consist of the followings except ?",
      answer1: "The propulsion system",
      answer2: "Antennas and transponders",
      answer3: "Transducers and breakers",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "4C",
    },

    {
      question:"The capability of a satellite to act as a repeater for many different earth stations is called ? ",
      answer1: "Voice Access",
      answer2: "Data Access",
      answer3: "Frequency Access",
      answer4: "Multiply Access",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "4D",
    },

    {
      question:"The satellite is usually placed in a geosynchronous orbit about ____ miles above the earth ?",
      answer1: "33200 miles",
      answer2: "22300 miles",
      answer3: "24800 miles ",
      answer4: "56000 miles",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "4E",
    },
  ],
};

export const TVQuiz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: `Television is used in the practical 
      of transmitting scenes or reception of ?`,
      answer1: "Video and Audio UHF or VHF Radio Signals",
      answer2: "Only Video Signal",
      answer3: "Only Audio Signal ",
      answer4: "Only High Frequency Image",
      correctAnswer: "answer1",
      key: "5A",
    },

    {
      question: "Which of these is not a television display technology ?",
      answer1: "Plasma display ",
      answer2: "Digital light processing ",
      answer3: "Light crystal display ",
      answer4: "Bill board display.",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "5B",
    },

    {
      question: "Which of these does not concern television ?",
      answer1: "Tuner ",
      answer2: "Blue bed ",
      answer3: "Amplifier",
      answer4: "Detector",
      correctAnswer: "answer2",
      key: "5C",
    },

    {
      question: `The television ____ by means of a 
      camera tube converts light rays into electric 
      electric signals ?`,
      answer1: "Receiver",
      answer2: "Transducer",
      answer3: "Modulator ",
      answer4: "Transmitter",
      correctAnswer: "answer4",
      key: "5D",
    },

    {
      question: `CRT stands for`,
      answer1: "Cathode Radio Transmitter ",
      answer2: "Cathode Resistor Transmitter ",
      answer3: "Cathode Ray Tube ",
      answer4: "Cathode Resistance Tube",
      correctAnswer: "answer3",
      key: "5E",
    },
  ],
};


